Mojtaba Namazi Fard

Software Engineer

DoB: 1998-08-03

Military Service: Served

anf.namazi@gmail.com

(+98)9210886520

(+98)9900890108

anfnamazi.github.io/Resume

Tehran, Iran

Profile Summary

Hi I'm a software engineer with 4 years of experience in front-end development, current tech stack is: TypeScript, React. Worked with 3 software companies on various project stages: requirements analysis, UI and product design, choosing tech stack, architecture design, and software development.

Skills



Work Experience

Front-End Developer

March 2019 - Present

Sharif hamrah pazhoohan

Tasks and Achievements

- Participated in the planning and execution of sprints, ensuring timely delivery of high-quality code.
- Implemented performance optimization strategies for adding large amounts of data to the map container.
- Conducted code reviews to maintain code quality and adherence to coding standards.

Front-End Developer

December 2020 - December 2021

Himart

Tasks and Achievements

- Optimized web applications for maximum speed and scalability, resulting in a 40% decrease in page load time and improve overall site traffic.
- Implemented strategies for filtering and sorting shops in near area.

Front-End Developer

September 2021 - December 2021

Dade kavan | Andishe bartar

Tasks and Achievements

Successfully led the redesign of food ordering process resulting improve user engagement.

Education

Bachelor of Software Engineering

Institute/University: Sadra

Language

English: Intermediate

Certificates

React October 2019

Institute: Sharif University Free Education

Social Network





